[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "Why are you doing it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "doing", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Well, I think a lot of mistruths have been written about Phoebe, and I think that it was time to take her back, to reclaim her as ours and to put an end to some of the stories that have been going around.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "mistruths", "have", "been", "written", "about", "Phoebe", ",", "and", "I", "think", "that", "it", "was", "time", "to", "take", "her", "back", ",", "to", "reclaim", "her", "as", "ours", "and", "to", "put", "an", "end", "to", "some", "of", "the", "stories", "that", "have", "been", "going", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "Were you taken aback by the kind of worldwide attention?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "taken", "aback", "by", "the", "kind", "of", "worldwide", "attention", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Very much so.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "much", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Is that what's really got to you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "'s", "really", "got", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "It was devastating to blame Phoebe.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "devastating", "to", "blame", "Phoebe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "August 2009?", "question_tokens": ["August", "2009", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["August 2009"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "What was the motivation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "motivation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "I was taking a career break.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "taking", "a", "career", "break", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Very different, I imagine, to the place you arrived to in America?", "question_tokens": ["Very", "different", ",", "I", "imagine", ",", "to", "the", "place", "you", "arrived", "to", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "How they would adapt?", "question_tokens": ["How", "they", "would", "adapt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "What kind of girl was she, Phoebe?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "girl", "was", "she", ",", "Phoebe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Extraordinarily intelligent and vivacious and a great sense of humor, and a foodie.", "answer_tokens": ["Extraordinarily", "intelligent", "and", "vivacious", "and", "a", "great", "sense", "of", "humor", ",", "and", "a", "foodie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Was she a confident girl?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "she", "a", "confident", "girl", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "In ways, she was.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "ways", ",", "she", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "What happened before that made you feel that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "before", "that", "made", "you", "feel", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Phoebe, she had -- she had a run-in with some girls before.", "answer_tokens": ["Phoebe", ",", "she", "had", "--", "she", "had", "a", "run-in", "with", "some", "girls", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "In Ireland?", "question_tokens": ["In", "Ireland", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ireland"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "What did they say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "they", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "That will be no problem.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "will", "be", "no", "problem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "When did you discover for the first time that Phoebe was being bullied?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "discover", "for", "the", "first", "time", "that", "Phoebe", "was", "being", "bullied", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "November.", "answer_tokens": ["November", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "What could you deduce?", "question_tokens": ["What", "could", "you", "deduce", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "She wouldn't tell me.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "would", "n't", "tell", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Did she ever say what it was about?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "ever", "say", "what", "it", "was", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["December"]}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CD", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Never?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Well, once in December she told me that one -- one of the girls involved in a new incident of bullying kept coming up to her in the hallways and screaming at her.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "once", "in", "December", "she", "told", "me", "that", "one", "--", "one", "of", "the", "girls", "involved", "in", "a", "new", "incident", "of", "bullying", "kept", "coming", "up", "to", "her", "in", "the", "hallways", "and", "screaming", "at", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "ORGAN: Did she know that these girls were using social media like Facebook and so on to bully her as well?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Did", "she", "know", "that", "these", "girls", "were", "using", "social", "media", "like", "Facebook", "and", "so", "on", "to", "bully", "her", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "TO", "RB", "PRP$", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "But she wasn't -- the bullying on Facebook, the cyber bullying that has been put out by people was just a small component of the bullying of Phoebe.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "she", "was", "n't", "--", "the", "bullying", "on", "Facebook", ",", "the", "cyber", "bullying", "that", "has", "been", "put", "out", "by", "people", "was", "just", "a", "small", "component", "of", "the", "bullying", "of", "Phoebe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last day"]}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Had she confided in anybody about how bad she was feeling?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "she", "confided", "in", "anybody", "about", "how", "bad", "she", "was", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "I don't think until the last day, really.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "until", "the", "last", "day", ",", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "This is a systematic abuse of somebody, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "a", "systematic", "abuse", "of", "somebody", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", ",", "``", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 206, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "One of the bullies the next day was overheard saying, \"done.\"", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "bullies", "the", "next", "day", "was", "overheard", "saying", ",", "``", "done", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "To drive somebody to suicide and they just put \"done\" on Facebook?", "question_tokens": ["To", "drive", "somebody", "to", "suicide", "and", "they", "just", "put", "``", "done", "''", "on", "Facebook", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "``", "NN", "''", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Well, she got what she deserved, that was another one.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "she", "got", "what", "she", "deserved", ",", "that", "was", "another", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Why were they so determined to force Phoebe into what eventually happened?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "they", "so", "determined", "to", "force", "Phoebe", "into", "what", "eventually", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "I honestly don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "honestly", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "It's wicked, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "wicked", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "It's astounding that there was never a stop mechanism, you know, internal stop mechanism for some of these kids to say, this is going too far.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "astounding", "that", "there", "was", "never", "a", "stop", "mechanism", ",", "you", "know", ",", "internal", "stop", "mechanism", "for", "some", "of", "these", "kids", "to", "say", ",", "this", "is", "going", "too", "far", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "What is your reaction when you see, again, Gus Sayer saying that so soon after Phoebe died?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "see", ",", "again", ",", "Gus", "Sayer", "saying", "that", "so", "soon", "after", "Phoebe", "died", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "It was -- it was very painful because, you know, you realize as a parent that no matter what I did, no matter how many times I called the school, no matter how many people I might have spoken to there, that she didn't stand a chance there.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "--", "it", "was", "very", "painful", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "realize", "as", "a", "parent", "that", "no", "matter", "what", "I", "did", ",", "no", "matter", "how", "many", "times", "I", "called", "the", "school", ",", "no", "matter", "how", "many", "people", "I", "might", "have", "spoken", "to", "there", ",", "that", "she", "did", "n't", "stand", "a", "chance", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gus Sayer", "Phoebe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "ORGAN: What did you find out after her death about what else had been going on that you weren't aware of?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "did", "you", "find", "out", "after", "her", "death", "about", "what", "else", "had", "been", "going", "on", "that", "you", "were", "n't", "aware", "of", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "I didn't know that there were a fairly good number of teachers who witnessed things.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "know", "that", "there", "were", "a", "fairly", "good", "number", "of", "teachers", "who", "witnessed", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "As a teacher or as a parent?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "teacher", "or", "as", "a", "parent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Maybe both.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "And as a mother?", "question_tokens": ["And", "as", "a", "mother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "As a mother, I think that had the school intervened the way they should have intervened, if they had followed up the way they should have followed up, that Phoebe would still be here.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "a", "mother", ",", "I", "think", "that", "had", "the", "school", "intervened", "the", "way", "they", "should", "have", "intervened", ",", "if", "they", "had", "followed", "up", "the", "way", "they", "should", "have", "followed", "up", ",", "that", "Phoebe", "would", "still", "be", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Do you feel that justice was done?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "justice", "was", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "I'd like to actually clarify, because I know that there are some journalists that -- that think that prison terms were on the cards.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "like", "to", "actually", "clarify", ",", "because", "I", "know", "that", "there", "are", "some", "journalists", "that", "--", "that", "think", "that", "prison", "terms", "were", "on", "the", "cards", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe", "Betsy Scheibel", "Beth"]}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBD", ":", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ":", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Do you feel that you got justice for Phoebe?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "you", "got", "justice", "for", "Phoebe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "I think even having the charges brought was - was justice for Phoebe and for so many other kids who are bullied that - what Betsy Scheibel and Beth did was they kind of threw down the gauntlet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "even", "having", "the", "charges", "brought", "was", "-", "was", "justice", "for", "Phoebe", "and", "for", "so", "many", "other", "kids", "who", "are", "bullied", "that", "-", "what", "Betsy", "Scheibel", "and", "Beth", "did", "was", "they", "kind", "of", "threw", "down", "the", "gauntlet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "I mean the circle of people that get so damaged by this kind of thing is huge, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "the", "circle", "of", "people", "that", "get", "so", "damaged", "by", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "is", "huge", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "It's massive.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "massive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Has she ever said anything to you, Sharon Velasquez?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "she", "ever", "said", "anything", "to", "you", ",", "Sharon", "Velasquez", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sharon Velasquez"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Nothing?", "question_tokens": ["Nothing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Never a word to you?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "a", "word", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Did any of them write you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "any", "of", "them", "write", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "ORGAN: Did you feel that remorse was sincere?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Did", "you", "feel", "that", "remorse", "was", "sincere", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "That these things are allowed to happen unless you put a lid on them?", "question_tokens": ["That", "these", "things", "are", "allowed", "to", "happen", "unless", "you", "put", "a", "lid", "on", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Why this case and what have been the repercussions legally since you took the actions you took?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "this", "case", "and", "what", "have", "been", "the", "repercussions", "legally", "since", "you", "took", "the", "actions", "you", "took", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Well, simply put the evidence brought us to the point where charges were appropriate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "simply", "put", "the", "evidence", "brought", "us", "to", "the", "point", "where", "charges", "were", "appropriate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "From a strictly legal point of view, how culpable do you think the school was in terms of not tackling this bullying before it was too late?", "question_tokens": ["From", "a", "strictly", "legal", "point", "of", "view", ",", "how", "culpable", "do", "you", "think", "the", "school", "was", "in", "terms", "of", "not", "tackling", "this", "bullying", "before", "it", "was", "too", "late", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "Well, we looked at the school behavior.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "looked", "at", "the", "school", "behavior", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Did you pick up on that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "pick", "up", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "How did that come about and what have been the implications of that for future cases now involving bullying?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "come", "about", "and", "what", "have", "been", "the", "implications", "of", "that", "for", "future", "cases", "now", "involving", "bullying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Well, they were tried as youthful offenders.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "were", "tried", "as", "youthful", "offenders", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "But do you feel that what happened with this case is making a real impact now on bullying in schools in America?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "feel", "that", "what", "happened", "with", "this", "case", "is", "making", "a", "real", "impact", "now", "on", "bullying", "in", "schools", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "I think in some ways, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "in", "some", "ways", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "In simple terms, what is that law?", "question_tokens": ["In", "simple", "terms", ",", "what", "is", "that", "law", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Well, it doesn't - essentially what it does is it mandates the schools to report incidences of bullying should they believe that that - an act is one of bullying.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "does", "n't", "-", "essentially", "what", "it", "does", "is", "it", "mandates", "the", "schools", "to", "report", "incidences", "of", "bullying", "should", "they", "believe", "that", "that", "-", "an", "act", "is", "one", "of", "bullying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Coming up , what would you like the legacy to be?", "question_tokens": ["Coming", "up", ",", "what", "would", "you", "like", "the", "legacy", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Well, ideally, I would like it to be that - to treat children in a more civilized manner and know boundaries.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "ideally", ",", "I", "would", "like", "it", "to", "be", "that", "-", "to", "treat", "children", "in", "a", "more", "civilized", "manner", "and", "know", "boundaries", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "What would you like the legacy to be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "like", "the", "legacy", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Well, ideally I would like it to be that humans just treat each other in a more civilized manner and no boundaries.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "ideally", "I", "would", "like", "it", "to", "be", "that", "humans", "just", "treat", "each", "other", "in", "a", "more", "civilized", "manner", "and", "no", "boundaries", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "You're not?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "No, I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "And actually if the legacy is that in future, schools are just more aware, they take more action earlier and some lives can be saved rather than lost because of what's happened, that is at least a positive that comes out of this hell for you, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "actually", "if", "the", "legacy", "is", "that", "in", "future", ",", "schools", "are", "just", "more", "aware", ",", "they", "take", "more", "action", "earlier", "and", "some", "lives", "can", "be", "saved", "rather", "than", "lost", "because", "of", "what", "'s", "happened", ",", "that", "is", "at", "least", "a", "positive", "that", "comes", "out", "of", "this", "hell", "for", "you", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "NN", "RBR", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]